

### Profile

Mobile Application Developer with around 2 years experience in software development lifecycle (SDLC) including analysis, design, development, and testing, deployment and documentation as per ISO standards. Experience in Mobile Application Operating systems like iOS and Android. Skilled, motivated and product-oriented mobile application developer with strong Object Oriented Programming Concepts and design skills Experience in developing android and iOS Apps.

# Employment History

## Mobile Developer Freelancer at Ideon Lab, Surabaya

January 2020 — Present

Freelancer of Mobile App Developer under Ideon Lab Software House that was build by myself.

## Mobile Developer at PT. Berbagi Solusi Teknologi, Jakarta

July 2020 — September 2020

Create Mobile App Front end for Social Funding Startup with Flutter and Firebase.

### Mobile Developer at Revo Apps, Surabaya

January 2020 — March 2022

Create Mobile App for hobbies marketplace (Indohobi,id) at Revo Apps Software house. Apps Already live and deployed to playstore and appstore.

# Mobile Developer at PT. Minasa Finteknologi Syariah, Jakarta

March 2021 — April 2022

Create Mobile Apps for Dana Daya Sejahtera Koperasi Digital. Apps is used for internal cooperative society. Social Funding. And more payment feature for e-wallet or bank transfer. Apps already deployed at Playstore and Appstore.

# Mobile Developer at Asset Data Solution Bh.d, Kuala Lumpur

January 2022 — Present

Create Mobile Apps for asset management system for several client such as Petronas, Sepura, and Air Asia under AssetData.io Platform. Apps already deployed at Playstore and Appstore.

## Education

# Bachelor Degree, Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember, Surabaya August 2017 — August 2021

Graduated with 3.34 GPA with thesis title is Automated Segmentation of Deep Vein Thrombosis using CNN with U-Net Architecture.

#### **Details**

Jakarta

Indonesia

+6281268786843

fradipta.alqaiyum@gmail.com

Date / Place of birth

12-01-1999

Bukittinggi

Nationality

Indonesian

#### Links

Github

LinkedIn

Personal Website

#### **Skills**

Git

Swift

Flutter

Firebase

Kotlin

## Languages

Bahasa

**English** 

#### **Hobbies**

Gaming, Travelling, Movies.

# Student Exchange, Nanyang Technological University, Singapore

March 2019 — March 2019

Student Exchange at Nanyang Technological University for 1 week.

## Courses

# Fundamental of Deep Learning for Computer Vision, NVIDIA

October 2019 — October 2019

## **Kotlin Programming, Dicoding**

June 2020 — June 2020

## **Dart Programming, Dicoding**

July 2022 — July 2022

# **Y** Extra-curricular activities

Assitant at B401 Multimedia Computing Laboratory, Surabaya

January 2019 — August 2022

Laboratory Assistant at B401 Multimedia Computing Laboratory at Sepuluh Nopember Institute of Technology, Surabaya, Indonesia.